It is a really good way to get your blood flowing and to get you ready for even more difficult things to come.
We are going to start with our left foot.
We are going to step with our left foot.
We are going to take our right foot step it behind, then you're going to take your left foot and step it out.
See you just go the other way.
You take your right foot and step it down and step your left foot behind and take your right foot and you step it out.
That is the basic bottom half move for your grapevine.
The top part is really optional.
If you just want to kind of groove, groove, groove and step and groove and groove and groove and step, that's your standard grapevine.
It is usually just going to go left and right or you can add a back and a forward and if you want to get really intricate you can just add a turn come here, two, three, and turn, two three, here.
Standard grapevine that is in pretty much every warm up.
So again it is going to go left, two, three, four, right, we'll go back and forward and that's your standard grapevine.